# **Dave Levine**

Sea Cliff, NY • 516.455.6778 https://cv.davelevine.io

dave@davelevine.io • LinkedIn: davelevine87

# IT Analyst with 8 years experience and a master's degree in Information Systems.

Experienced IT analyst with comprehensive knowledge of developing, documenting and delivering solutions for attaining business goals. Capable of leading cross-functional teams to advance continuous improvement of web-based solutions for clinical faculty and staff.

#### **Technical Proficiencies:**

Platforms: Linux, MacOS, Windows

Skills: Virtualization, Cloud Services (AWS), Containerization, Shell Scripting, CI/CD, YAML, JSON, XML

Methodologies: Software Development Life Cycle (SDLC), ITIL, Agile Development

Certifications: AWS Certified Solutions Architect - Associate

### **Professional Experience**

## IT Business Analyst | Weill Cornell Medicine, New York, NY

December 2017 - Present

- Lead analyst and subject matter expert (SME) for the Conflicts of Interest module.
- Manage workflow of administrative approvals, training and documentation required for the advancement of over 5,000 research studies.
- Liaise with stakeholders to collect business requirements, create functional specifications, distribute data & interface with cross-functional teams.
- Conduct quality control testing used to improve workflows and enhance business processes.

# Application Support Analyst II | Weill Cornell Medicine, New York, NY

October 2015 - December 2017

- Provided Tier 2 end-user support for research administration application modules.
- Provisioned user access rights to research administration application modules.
- Collaborated with lead analysts in the implementation, testing & training for new and enhanced functionality.
- Created and developed knowledge base to store documentation, procedures & solutions related to research administration application modules.

#### Systems Support Analyst | ClickIT Inc., Hauppauge, NY

November 2013 – October 2015

- Provided Tier 1 end-user support for MS Windows based system support & proprietary surveillance software.
- Conducted video analytics testing to improve motion detection, heat maps & people counting.
- Created and maintained company knowledge base.

### Education

#### **Master of Science in Information Systems**

**Graduated 2014** 

Long Island University, New York, NY

### **Bachelor of Science in Information Management & Technology**

Graduated 2011

Long Island University, New York, NY

#### **Additional Skills**